I have a plan that I want to talk to you about.
I think most of you are already subscribing to the channel
You like the contents of the channel. I want to improve it.
There are some things about the videos, especially the videos of the lectures, that I do not like very much.
And I think you are not satisfied either.
First of all, I think the videos lack proper visuals.
There are also some parts of the videos that are specific to students in my classroom only.
Like information about exams and so on. And there are other parts of the videos that are not audible.
Or when digression is not appropriate
Also, there are lectures for years on the same topic
Which should be standardized in a specific way in order to be properly understood and defined.
Also, I would like the text of the lectures to be accessible to all, and it would be better if the lectures were entitled.
The text of the lectures will help with this. Then after this it will be possible to translate the lectures.
I have some volunteers working on this right now.
So I created a page on a site called Petreon.
Petrion allows people who are interested in content, let's move a YouTube channel like this,
To assist in the continuous development of the projects that are being shared there.
So ... if you are interested in participating in this and want to see the things I have described
Click and subscribe to maybe this will be a good thing.
This is what I wanted to share.